Guide to the Cornell University Women's Studies Program records, 1968-1997.
Cornell University Women's Studies Program records
- Staff/Community Elections, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Faculty Study Group, 1979-1983 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Study Groups, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Study Groups, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Course Publicity, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Course Publicity, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Open House, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Special Projects Money, Travel Money, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Memos to Teaching Faculty, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Committees, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Committees, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Committees, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Visiting Scholars Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Visiting Scholars Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Women's Studies Visiting Scholars, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Tulis McCall, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Sonia Johnson, 1981-82 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Rhoda Linton/Rayna Rapp, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Monique Wittig, Mary Ruggie, Jean Kennard, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Natalie Davis, Paula Treichler, Rayna Rapp, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Michelle Cliff, Beth Brant, Evelyn Beck, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Kathleen Frankovic, Katerina Angelaki-Rooke, Allison Jaggar, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Olga Finlay, Lenora Rodriguez Lescano, Tom Holloway, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Amiya Rao, Juliet Mitchell, Holly Near, Alice Cook, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Ellie Smeal, Cigdem Kagitcibasi, Magda Enriquez, Bernadette Bucher, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Nicole Loraux, Pietro Pucci, Bella Abzug, Gail Omredt, Lenore Weitzman, Mary Felstiner, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Rosalyn Terborg-Penn, Nina Baym, Carol Stack, Mary Helen Washington, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- WID Conference, Women and Law Conference, Black America Conference, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Women, Peace and Conflict, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Narratives, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Public Events Calendar, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Related Events, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Co-Sponsorship Request Inquiries, Co-Sponsorship Events, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Diacritics - Nuclear Criticism, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- GAYPAC - 15th Anniversary, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Prizes and Awards Committee, Curriculum and Advising Committee, 1981-1986 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Political Liason, 1981-1990 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Search Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Search, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Search, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Laura X - Date Rape (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Women's Studies: M. Jacobus, J. Fortune, S. McConnell-Ginet, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Women's Studies: M. Hite, J. Brumberg, C. Mohanty, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Women's Studies: C. A. Martin, J. Blackall, Meyers and Katzenstein, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Fortune - 3 Year Review (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Fortune - 3 Year Review (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Graduate Minor Information, 1973-1985 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Library Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Committees: Non Faculty Appointments, Course Publicty, Public Events, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Publicity, 1981-1985 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Public Events, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Graduate Faculty Representatives, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Graduate Faculty Representatives, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Symposium, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Course Budget, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Women's Studies - Freshmen Seminars, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- March - Holmberg Fund, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Clark Award, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Audio Visual Materials, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Women's Studies: Bem, Blackall, Brumberg, Collins, Engelstein, Ford, Fortune, Hite, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Women's Studies: Holmberg, Lewontin, March, Meyers, Katzenstein, Mohanty, Norton, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Women's Studies: Schwartzbach, Silverberg, Saadawi, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Joan Brumberg Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Joan Brumberg Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Joan Brumberg Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Joan Brumberg Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Judy Kram Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Kram Award, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Kram Award, 1980-1986 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Kram Award Applicants, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Kram Award Applicants, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Kram Award Applicants, 1984-1988 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Kram Award Recipiant: Cynthia McKeown, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Kram Award Recipiants: Donna Goldstein, Lisa Aronson, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Kram Award Recipiant: Eileen Craig, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Kram Award Recipiant: Lisa Norling, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Kram Award Recipiant Susan Nelligan:, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Women's Studies Conference - Hamilton College, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Feminist Scholars Conference, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- SUNY Women's Studies Council, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- 1/2 Vacant Line, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- WID Grad Students, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Women's Hall of Fame (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Women's History Workshop, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Cornell Women's Center, 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Women Direct Series, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Women's Encampment, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- WID Professors, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Students Concentrating on Women's Studies, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Women's Studies Core Curriculum, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Women's Task Force University of Virginia, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Women and Professionalism, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Public Events Calendar, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Requests for Co-Sponsorship, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Men's Awareness Week, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Elina Haavio-Mannila, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Committees, 1984-1989 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Memos to Teaching Faculty, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Women's Studies - International, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Women's Studies: Shirley Malcolm, Margaret Rossiter, Ruth Bleier, Charles Rosenberg, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Women's Studies: Kate Kasten, Andrea Lowenstein, Grace Paley, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Women's Studies: Nellie McKay, Tatyana Mamonova, Susan Williams, Paula Caplan, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Women's Studies: Susan Bell, William Bennett, Caroline Bynum, Julie d'Acci, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Women's Studies: Geraldine Ferraro, Ellen Goodman, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Women's Studies: Elizabeth Holtzman, Susan Ware, Rayna Rapp, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Women's Studies: Connie Shapiro, Susan Suleiman, Carol Vance, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Linda Williams - Potential Visiting Scholar, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Reorganization of Board, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Betty Falcao, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Cornell Council, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Social History of American Medicine Program, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Polytechnic of North London, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Governor's Office - "Division for Women", 1986 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Executive Board Review, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Executive Board Review, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Executive Board Review, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Executive Board Review, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1978-1984 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1978-1984 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Evaluation of Cornell Women's Studies Program, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Steering Committee, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Steering Committee, 1972-1978 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Steering Committee Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1986-1991 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Steering Committee Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Program Proposals, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Intersession Program on Women, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Seminar: Black and White Women, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Women's Studies Lectures (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Charter Revisions, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Publicity and News, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Gifts to Women's Studies, 1972-1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Gifts to Women's Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Donor Thank You Letters, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Retreat, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Humanities Council, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Women's Studies" Berlant, Crane, Crenshaw, Einstein, Fraser, Lapidus, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Intro to Women's Studies - B. Martin, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Women's Studies: Miller-Bernal, Press, Scheman, Snitow, Widmer, Willis, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Women's Studies: Sheila Tobias, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Professor's-at-Large, 1979-84 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Professor's-at-Large: Barbara Jordan, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Correspondence: Alice Cook, 1973-1977 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Conference: Women in Science, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Conference: Anti Feminism, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Conference: Grant Requests, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Conference: Future of Women's Studies, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Development and Conference Speakers, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Women's Study Conference, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Anniversary Conference, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Anniversary Conference, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Letters, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Letters, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Curriculum Vitas, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Mailing Lists, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Newsletters, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Newsletters, 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Newsletters, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Announcements, 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Syllabi and Course Material, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Syllabi and Course Material, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Syllabi and Course Material, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Syllabi and Course Material, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Syllabi and Course Material, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Syllabi and Course Material, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Syllabi and Course Material, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Old Course Lists, 1987-1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Affirmative Action, 1972-1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Affirmative Action, 1977-1982 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Information, 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Annual Report, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Annual Report, 1978-1981 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Annual Report, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Annual Report, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Annual Report, 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)